Walter B. Wriston Papers MS134
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Speeches, 1951 -- 2003; 1980 -- 1999; MS134.001; 8.0 Linear Feet; 24 Digital Object(s)
  - [The Great Disconnect] Boston, 2000-10-02; MS134.001.038.00046 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Great Disconnect] Boston, 2000-10-02; MS134.001.038.00047 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Great Disconnect] Boston, 2000-10-02; MS134.001.038.00048 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Great Disconnect] Measure, 2000-10-20; MS134.001.038.00049 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - Global accounting for a global market, 2002; MS134.001.038.00050 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Speech regarding the Wriston professorship at Fletcher School] Chair, 2003-12-18; MS134.001.038.00051 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Reflections on the Life of Cedric Grant] Rick Grant, 2003; MS134.001.038.00052 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Fletcher in the Information Age] Fletcher, 2003-06-18 -- 2003-09-03; MS134.001.038.00053 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Fletcher in the Information Age] Fletcher, 2003-06-18 -- 2003-09-03; MS134.001.038.00054 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Fletcher in the Information Age] Fletcher, 2003-07-08 -- 2003-09-03; MS134.001.038.00055 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Fletcher in the Information Age] Fletcher, 2003-07-21 -- 2003-09-03; MS134.001.038.00056 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Fletcher in the Information Age] Fletcher, 2003-07-23 -- 2003-09-03; MS134.001.038.00057 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Fletcher in the Information Age] Fletcher, 2003-07-29 -- 2003-09-03; MS134.001.038.00058 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Fletcher in the Information Age] Fletcher, 2003-07-30 -- 2003-09-03; MS134.001.038.00059 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Fletcher in the Information Age] Fletcher, 2003-08-11 -- 2003-09-03; MS134.001.038.00060 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Fletcher in the Information Age] Fletcher, 2003-08-12 -- 2003-09-03; MS134.001.038.00061 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Fletcher in the Information Age] Fletchertoshultz, 2003-09-03; MS134.001.038.00062 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
- Books, 1982 -- 2007; 1982 -- 2006; MS134.002; 7.7 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes
  This series contains material relating to Walter B. Wriston's three published books: "Risk and Other Four-Letter Words" (1986), "The Twilight of Sovereignty: How the Information Revolution is Transforming Our World" (1992) and "Bites, Bytes, & Balance Sheets: The New Economic Rules of Engagement In a Wireless World" (2007). Wriston frequently spoke and wrote about banking, the impact of information technology, and other economic issues. He used his speeches and articles to form the basis of his books.
  Material in this series includes multiple drafts of each book and drafts of individual chapters, as well as material related to the books, such as source material, reviews, and correspondence. Materials relating to each book were kept together and have been grouped by type, such as complete drafts, chapter drafts, source material, publication information, and correspondence. Material in box 042 relates to publication rights, contracts, royalties, and finances for Wriston's books and is restricted for 75 years.
  "Risk and Other Four-Letter Words"
  Wriston's first book, "Risk & Other Four-Letter Words" was published in 1986 by Harper and Row Publishers, now HarperCollins. It is an edited compilation of his speeches on contemporary banking and economic issues. The collection includes two reviews for the book and a bound copy of the text. The speeches used as the source material for this text are included in series 001.
  "The Twilight of Sovereignty"
  Wriston's second book, "The Twilight of Sovereignty: How the Information Revolution is Transforming Our World" was first published in September 1992 by Charles Scribner's Sons. This book is also referenced by its original working title, "The Information Revolution." Material in the collection includes the 1987 book proposal and various drafts from 1987 to 1992. Some drafts have handwritten notations and corrections. The drafts are arranged chronologically when possible. Some of the draft materials are printed out files extracted from Wriston's computers. Some of these files are saved on a CD-ROM titled "CD_Rom_WBW_Computer Files", which is located in series 004.
  In addition to drafts of the book, the "Twilight" material also contains correspondence between Wriston and his publishers from 1990-1993. The bulk of these letters are from Edward "Ned" T. Chase, senior editor at Charles Scribner's Sons. These letters document discussions of the book's index and book jacket, as well as plans for promoting the book and requests for reviews. Chase also sent a number of current newspaper and journal articles to incorporate into the text. Wriston's other correspondents from Scribner's include Hamilton Cain, assistant editor; Bill Goldstein, senior editor; and Charles Flowers, assistant editor. There is also a memo from Richard Vigilante, editor of "The City Journal", who assisted in editing the book. Other correspondence, ranging from 1992-1996, are primarily letters of thanks for autographed copies of the book and letters from people who read the book or saw Wriston during press junkets. Wriston's sixth grade teacher, Martha Sorensen, also sent a letter commenting on the book.
  Reviews for "The Twilight of Sovereignty" are arranged chronologically from 1992-1993. The reviews consist of photocopies, torn out pages, and bound volumes of journals and newspapers.
  "Bites, Bytes, & Balance Sheets"
  Wriston's third and final book, "Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: The New Economic Rules of Engagement In a New Wireless World" was published posthumously by Hoover Institution Press in 2007. Material in the collection includes drafts of the manuscript and of individual chapters, as well as source material, publication material, and correspondence. Some of the draft materials are printed out files extracted from Wriston's computer and saved on a CD-ROM titled "CD_Rom_WBW_Computer Files", which is located in series 004.
  Prior to Wriston's death in 2005, he was working on a new manuscript entitled, "The Quick and the Dead: The New Economic Rules of Engagement For A Wired (and Wireless) World". In 2000, Wriston was in the process of editing the manuscript and locating a publisher when, due to illness, the book was put on hold. After Wriston's death, his wife Kathryn Wriston hired editor John McCarty and Kurt Willett to complete the manuscript. The book was extended to ten chapters and re-titled, "Bits, Bytes, And Balance Sheets: The New Economic Rules of Engagement In a New Wireless World." The posthumous additions to the manuscript were created from the speeches written by Wriston from 1994-2002. Although Wriston had been ill, he continued to write speeches and, when possible, attend speaking engagements. The Honorable George P. Shultz, a close friend of Wriston's, wrote a forward for the revised manuscript and Kathryn Wriston wrote an afterword. The Hoover Institution Press annotated "Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets" with updated economic data prior to publication.
  The materials in this series are arranged chronologically by book. Materials accessioned and processed in 2009 are arranged in a second chronological run at the end of the series.
  75 years from the date of creation. Open for research.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Draft One, 1982 -- 1987; MS134.002.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Draft Two, 1985 -- 1986; MS134.002.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Draft Three, 1987; MS134.002.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Draft Four, 1987; MS134.002.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Draft Five, 1987 -- 1988; MS134.002.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 09 & Insert, MS134.002.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 10, MS134.002.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 12, MS134.002.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Binder - Chapters 1-5 & Quote by George Bernard Shaw, MS134.002.016.00009 (Box 16)
    These materials were removed from a binder which was not archivally sound.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Binder - Chapters 06-12, except 08, MS134.002.017.00001 (Box 17)
    These materials were removed from a binder which was not archivally sound. Two additional copies of Chapters 9 and 12 were in the back pocket of the binder.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 01, 1989; MS134.002.017.00002 (Box 17)
    This is a printout of a file from the folder titled Book as of 6/28/90 from the CD-ROM labeled CD_Rom_WBW_Computer Files. The date for the file is the last date it was modified.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1990; MS134.002.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1990; MS134.002.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 05, 1990; MS134.002.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 06, 1990; MS134.002.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 07, 1990; MS134.002.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 08, 1990; MS134.002.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 09, 1989; MS134.002.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 10, 1990; MS134.002.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 11, 1990; MS134.002.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 12, 1990; MS134.002.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Forward, 2005; MS134.002.017.00014 (Box 17)
    This is a printout of a file from the folder titled CTMacProfessional from the CD-ROM labeled CD_Rom_WBW_Computer Files. The date for the file is the last date it was modified. The file was modified after Walter Wriston's death.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 01, 2005; MS134.002.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 2005; MS134.002.017.00016 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 2005; MS134.002.017.00017 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 2005; MS134.002.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 2005; MS134.002.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 2005; MS134.002.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 2005; MS134.002.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 2005; MS134.002.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03 Footnotes, 2005; MS134.002.017.00023 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 2005; MS134.002.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 05, 2005; MS134.002.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 06, 2005; MS134.002.017.00026 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 06, 2005; MS134.002.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 07, 2005; MS134.002.017.00028 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 08, 2005; MS134.002.017.00029 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 09, 2005; MS134.002.017.00030 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 09 Quotes, 2005; MS134.002.017.00031 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 10, 2005; MS134.002.017.00032 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 12, 2005; MS134.002.017.00033 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 01, 1989; MS134.002.017.00034 (Box 17)
    This is a printout of a file from the folder titled Untitled Chapter 2feb 1991 from the CD-ROM labeled CD_Rom_WBW_Computer Files. The date for the file is the last date it was modified.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.017.00035 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1991; MS134.002.017.00036 (Box 17)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1991; MS134.002.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1991; MS134.002.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 05, 1991; MS134.002.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 06, 1991; MS134.002.018.00006 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 07, 1991; MS134.002.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 09, 1991; MS134.002.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 01, 1989; MS134.002.018.00009 (Box 18)
    This is a printout of a file from the folder titled Book 3_9_91 from the CD-ROM labeled CD_Rom_WBW_Computer Files. The date for the file is the last date it was modified.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1990; MS134.002.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.018.00011 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.018.00012 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.018.00013 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.018.00014 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.018.00015 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.018.00016 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.018.00017 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1991; MS134.002.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1991; MS134.002.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 05, 1991; MS134.002.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 05, 1991; MS134.002.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 06, 1991; MS134.002.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 06, 1990; MS134.002.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 07, 1990; MS134.002.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 08, 1990; MS134.002.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 08, 1991; MS134.002.018.00031 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 09, 1989; MS134.002.018.00032 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 10, 1990; MS134.002.018.00033 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 11, 1990; MS134.002.018.00034 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 12, 1990; MS134.002.018.00035 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Vigilante Sources, 1991; MS134.002.018.00036 (Box 18)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 01, 1989; MS134.002.018.00037 (Box 18)
    This is a printout of a file from the folder titled Book on 18 July 91 from the CD-ROM labeled CD_Rom_WBW_Computer Files. The date for the file is the last date it was modified.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1990; MS134.002.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1991; MS134.002.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1991; MS134.002.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 05, 1991; MS134.002.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 05, 1991; MS134.002.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 06, 1990; MS134.002.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 06, 1991; MS134.002.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 07, 1990; MS134.002.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 07, 1991; MS134.002.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 08, 1991; MS134.002.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 09, 1991; MS134.002.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 10, 1990; MS134.002.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 10, 1991; MS134.002.019.00027 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 11, 1991; MS134.002.019.00028 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 12, 1990; MS134.002.019.00029 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Vigilante Sources, 1991; MS134.002.019.00030 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Foreword, 1992; MS134.002.019.00031 (Box 19)
    This is a printout of a file from the folder titled Book3Aug91 from the CD-ROM labeled CD_Rom_WBW_Computer Files. The date for the file is the last date it was modified.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 01, 1989; MS134.002.019.00032 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1990; MS134.002.019.00033 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.019.00034 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.019.00035 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.019.00036 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.019.00037 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.019.00038 (Box 19)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.020.00004 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1990; MS134.002.020.00005 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1991; MS134.002.020.00006 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1991; MS134.002.020.00007 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.020.00008 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.020.00009 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.020.00010 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.020.00011 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 05, 1991; MS134.002.020.00012 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 05, 1991; MS134.002.020.00013 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 06, 1991; MS134.002.020.00014 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 06, 1990; MS134.002.020.00015 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 07, 1990; MS134.002.020.00016 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 07, 1991; MS134.002.020.00017 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 08, 1991; MS134.002.020.00018 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 09, 1991; MS134.002.020.00019 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 10, 1990; MS134.002.020.00020 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 10, 1991; MS134.002.020.00021 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 11, 1991; MS134.002.020.00022 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 12, 1990; MS134.002.020.00023 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Vigilante Sources, 1991; MS134.002.020.00024 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 01, 1991; MS134.002.020.00025 (Box 20)
    This is a printout of a file from the folder titled Book as of 9_16_91 from the CD-ROM labeled CD_Rom_WBW_Computer Files. The date for the file is the last date it was modified.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 02, 1991; MS134.002.020.00026 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 03, 1991; MS134.002.020.00027 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 04, 1991; MS134.002.020.00028 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 05, 1991; MS134.002.020.00029 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 06, 1991; MS134.002.020.00030 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 07, 1991; MS134.002.020.00031 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 07, 1991; MS134.002.020.00032 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 08, 1991; MS134.002.020.00033 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 08, 1991; MS134.002.020.00034 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 09, 1991; MS134.002.020.00035 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapter 10, 1991; MS134.002.020.00036 (Box 20)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Chapters 1-10, 1991; MS134.002.021.00001 (Box 21)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Setting Copy (Chapters 1-7), 1992; MS134.002.021.00002 (Box 21)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Setting Copy (Chapters 8-10), 1992; MS134.002.021.00003 (Box 21)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: How the Information Revolution is Transforming Our World by Walter B. Wriston, 1992; MS134.002.021.00004 (Box 21)
    Hardcover edition.
    Information technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Charles Scribner's Sons Publishers Correspondence, 1990 -- 1992; MS134.002.021.00005 (Box 21)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Charles Scribner's Sons Publishers Correspondence, 1992 -- 1993; MS134.002.021.00006 (Box 21)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Correspondence, 1992 -- 1996; MS134.002.022.00001 (Box 22)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty: Book Reviews, 1992 -- 1993; MS134.002.022.00002 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material for the Preface, 1999; MS134.002.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material for Chapter 01, 1999 -- 2002; MS134.002.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material for Chapter 02, 1994 -- 2000; MS134.002.022.00005 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material for Chapter 03, 1996 -- 1997; MS134.002.022.00006 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material for Chapter 04, 1999; MS134.002.022.00007 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material for Chapter 05, 1995 -- 1998; MS134.002.022.00008 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material for Chapters 06 and 07, 2000; MS134.002.022.00009 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material for Chapter 08, 2000; MS134.002.022.00010 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material for Chapter 09, 2002; MS134.002.022.00011 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material for Chapter 10, 2002 -- 2006; MS134.002.022.00012 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material, 1992; MS134.002.022.00013 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material, 1993; MS134.002.022.00014 (Box 22)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material, 1994 -- 1995; MS134.002.023.00001 (Box 23)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material, 1996; MS134.002.023.00002 (Box 23)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material, 1997; MS134.002.023.00003 (Box 23)
  - Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets: Source Material, 1998; MS134.002.023.00004 (Box 23)